<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>julia on Julia Recepies</title><link>https://anupjoseph.github.io/jlrecepies/tags/julia/</link><description>Recent content in julia on Julia Recepies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:17:41 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anupjoseph.github.io/jlrecepies/tags/julia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Read CSV files</title><link>https://anupjoseph.github.io/jlrecepies/posts/read-csv-files/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:17:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://anupjoseph.github.io/jlrecepies/posts/read-csv-files/</guid><description>Never Resting. A dream of Spring. Fire and blood. When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. A dream of Spring. Words are like wind. A dream of Spring. You know nothing, Jon Snow. The tourney of Ashford Meadows. The Knight of Lemonwood. And now his watch is ended. A good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act the good.</description><content>&lt;p>Never Resting. A dream of Spring. Fire and blood. When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. A dream of Spring. Words are like wind. A dream of Spring. You know nothing, Jon Snow. The tourney of Ashford Meadows. The Knight of Lemonwood. And now his watch is ended. A good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act the good. Each should have its own reward. The rains of castamere. The battle of the redgrass field. A good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act the good. Each should have its own reward. The tourney of Ashford Meadows. Can a man still be brave if he&amp;rsquo;s afraid? That is the only time a man can be brave. A good act does not wash out the bad, nor a bad act the good. Each should have its own reward. It is rare to meet a Lannister who shares my enthusiasm for dead Lannisters =&amp;gt;.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-python" data-lang="python">&lt;span style="color:#f92672">import&lt;/span> csv
pd&lt;span style="color:#f92672">.&lt;/span>read_csv(&lt;span style="color:#e6db74">&amp;#34;rfopop&amp;#34;&lt;/span>)
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div></content></item></channel></rss>